http://www.rightline.net/home/privacy.html

RightLine Privacy Policy
RightLine Privacy Statement:
RightLine (Pro Right Line Corp) is dedicated to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our privacy policy and
clarifies how we use the personal information that we obtain from our users.
Please read the following text. It explains our practices regarding your personal information, and how they relate to you when
you use our services.
This statement defines our current privacy practice. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will announce it on
our website. Should you have any questions or comments about this statement, please contact us at feed-back@rightline.net.
- RightLine collects a limited amount of information from our readers. This allows us to provide useful content and advertising
that is of interest to our readers. We request your name, email address, and other personal information when you signup to use our services.
- RightLine performs research based on the information you give us when you register on our website, take part in a survey, contest or other promotion. The
information is analyzed only in an aggregated fashion.
Whenever you place an order with RightLine, we ask for your name, telephone number, mailing address, email address and credit card information. This information is used to
process your order. If needed, we may use this information to contact you about the details of your order.
In addition to processing your order, RightLine sometimes uses the information to let you know about services or products we think may be of interest to you.
RightLine will not divulge any information regarding individual users, except as explained in this Privacy Statement, or to conform with applicable laws or legal
process, or to protect RightLine rights or property.
RightLine does not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to any advertiser.
RightLine will release your personal information only to the degree required to complete your order and charge your credit card. We contract with Verisign/PayPal Manager (a credit
card processing company) to validate your card number and process your transaction.
When you register with RightLine or sign up for any our services, we will contact you via email with information about our services and products, or other services
and products we believe you may be interested in. Only RightLine or people working for us under confidentiality agreements will contact you.
If you don't want to receive these offers and mailings, or if you want to stop future mailings, or correct or change any information we have about you, just let us
know by clicking on the Unsubscribe link in any email we send you, or send an email to publisher@rightline.net or calling 800-737-4518. We are available to take your call weekdays from 9 am to 5 pm CT. We'll remove your name from
our lists within ten days of receipt.
RightLine reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Statement at any time. We will notify you via email of any significant or material change. We will also
give you the opportunity to discontinue any further use of your information.
Some of our partners and advertisers link from our web site to their web sites where they sell their own products and services. Should you click on these links, be
aware that these other vendors have their own privacy practices. RightLine has no responsibility or liability for these autonomous sites. For more information regarding
the privacy policies of a web site, directly contact that specific site.
RightLine OnLine Stock Trading Report Home
Contact RightLine
Terms Of Use,
Subscriber Terms & Conditions, and
Privacy Policy
Copyright / Pro Right Line Corporation - All Rights Reserved
Online Stock Trading - Stock Splits - Buy Stock, Trade Stock - Stock Market Trading
Stock Trading - Investing Online - Internet Stock Trading
